## Mateeb Alharbi

Frontend Developer

Mateeb2000@gmail.com

966560046457

mateeb.surge.sh

linkedin.com/in/mateeb-alharbi in

github.com/Mateeb11 🕠

A fresh Computer Science graduate, and a Front-end web developer using React and Angular. My Passion is to build modern and responsive websites. As a Frontend developer, I'm interested in the UX/UI field and how to improve the user experience, so that I can learn how to implement new ideas and user experience.

## **EDUCATION**

## O Bachelor - Computer Science Umm AL-Qura University

05/2018 - 06/2023

3.71 / 4 GPA with second honors

## **PROJECTS**

## Multi-step form (05/2023 - 05/2023)

- A frontend mentor challenge for a multi-step form, the form have input validation and feedbacks. The website is responsive for all screen sizes. Made with React, Sass (preprocessor scripting language that is interpreted or compiled into CSS). All the CSS is done by me and I didn't use any library or framework.
- Try it here: https://aback-icicle.surge.sh
- https://github.com/Mateeb11/multi-step-form

## Easybank landing page (04/2023 - 05/2023)

- A frontend mentor challenge for building a landing page for a company, the website is responsive for all screen sizes. Made with React, Sass. All the CSS is done by me and I didn't use any library or framework.
- Try it here: https://gifted-selection.surge.sh
- https://github.com/Mateeb11/easybank-landing-page-master

# REST Countries API with color theme switcher (04/2023 - 04/2023)

- A frontend mentor challenge for a website that fetches data from REST API about countries. Also, it has dark and light mode switching. Made with react, react-router-dom, and redux-toolkit.
- Try it here: https://humdrum-smell.surge.sh
- https://shorturl.at/clsw2

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Elite Specialist | Tech GDP

Mobily

06/2024 - Present Riyadh

Junior Software Engineer

WAKI

11/2023 - Present Jeddah

**Junior Software Developer** 

Misk traineeship program at WAKI

08/2023 - 10/2023 Jeddah

IOT and software development

Smart Methods · Internship الأساليب الذكية

06/2022 - 08/2022 Makkah

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**



## **SOFT SKILLS**

Teamwork, Problem Solving, Communication, Self Management, Creativity, Willing to Learn.

#### CERTIFICATES

Misk skills - Nanodegree Program - Intro To Programming (04/2020 - 05/2020) At Udacity

## **INTERESTS**

Web Development Machine Learning

UX/UI Design